[
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$(a+2)(a+3)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "a^2+5a+6",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$(a+5)(a+3b)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "a^2+3ab+5a+15b",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$(x+3)(x+4)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "x^2+7x+12",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$(a+2b)(a-2b)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "a^2-4b^2",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$(x+3y)(4x-3y)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "4x^2+9xy-9y^2",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$(2x+3)(x+5)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "2x^2+13x+15",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$(a+b)(a+b)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "a^2+2ab+b^2",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$(x-2)(x^2+3x+4)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "x^3+x^2-2x-8",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$(3x+2y)(x-y)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "3x^2+x y-2y^2",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$(x+2y)(x^2-2xy+y^2)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "x^3+2y^3",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$(2x^2-3y)(x^3-y^3)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "2x^5-2x^2y^3-3x^3y+3y^4",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$(a+2b)(a^2-2ab+4b^2)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "a^3+8b^3",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$(x-3)(x^2+3x+9)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "x^3-27",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$(2a+b)(a^2-ab+b^2)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "2a^3+a^2b-ab^2+b^3",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$(x^2+2x)(x+3)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "x^3+5x^2+6x",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$(a-b)(a^2+ab+b^2)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "a^3-b^3",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$(x+4)(x^2-4x+16)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "x^3+64",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$(3x-2y)(x^2+xy+y^2)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "3x^3+x^2y-x y^2-2y^3",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$(2x^2+3y)(x^2-2y^2)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "2x^4-4x^2y^2+3x^2y-6y^3",
        "explanation": ""
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Oblicz $$(x^2+2xy+y^2)(x-y)$$",
        "latexAnswer": "x^3-x^2y-xy^2+y^3",
        "explanation": ""
    }
]
